<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://www.androiddeveloperdays.com/github2015/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.androiddeveloperdays.com/github2015/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 21:24:23 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 21:24:23 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>March Newsletter: Continuing to announce Featured Speakers</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the March newsletter :) We will be sharing updates with you in this newsletter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/posts/deadline_en.jpg&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 300px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call For Papers is still open. You can submit a talk from &lt;a href=&quot;/github2015/blog/share-your-knowledge-and-experience-in-add/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We listen to you. What do you want to see at ADD? Please share your ideas with this &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/16RB2PM-ifAxv4HqTOXWO72DlgYEEWc0f9SB921smTBs/viewform&quot;&gt;this form&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of people requesting participation to ADD has passed &lt;strong&gt;1175&lt;/strong&gt;. Hurry up to participate and fill &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.eventbrite.com/e/android-developer-days-2015-registration-14846274607&quot;&gt;this form&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/posts/AttendeegeoWMarch7.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/tim-messerschmidt.jpg&quot; /&gt;	
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
    As a long time mobile and web developer, Tim Messerschmidt channels his knowledge and experience as Braintree&#39;s Head of Developer Relation. He is passionate about startups and served as mentor at multiple incubators and accelerators.
    Prior to joining PayPal, Tim worked with Neofonie Mobile and Samsung focusing on several mobile projects. In his spare time, he leads and creates training classes in all sorts of developer-oriented topics, contributes to Open Source projects and is one of the authors of the Mobile Developer’s Guide to the Galaxy. In addition, he authored numerous articles published in print magazines.	
	&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/abhisek-devkota.png&quot; /&gt;	
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
	Abhisek Devkota is the Community Manager and project manager for Cyanogen Inc. The CyanogenMod Project is an openÂ­source distribution that is community driven and created in collaboration with volunteers around the world, with the goal to allow users to truly own their phone through customization, functionality and enhanced security over their personal data.
	&lt;/p&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/wiebe-elsinga.jpg&quot; /&gt;	
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
    Besides being a recent GDE for Android, Wiebe Elsinga is also an Android Developer with a passion for UX and design. Co-Founder/Organizer of the Google Developer Group Dutch Android User Group and working at Itude Mobile. Basically a EntrepreNerd.
    Mainly focused on the design and development of mobile applications.
	&lt;/p&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/markus-eisele.jpg&quot; /&gt;	
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
	Markus Eisele is a Developer Advocate at Red Hat and focuses on JBoss Middleware. He is working with Java EE servers from different vendors since more than 14 years and talks about his favorite topics around Java EE on conferences all over the world. He has been a principle consultant and worked with different customers on all kinds of Java EE related applications and solutions. Beside that he has always been a prolific blogger, writer and tech editor for different Java EE related books. He is an active member of the German DOAG e.V. and it&#39;s representative on the iJUG e.V. He is well known in the community as a Java Champion.
	&lt;/p&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/cyril-mottier.jpg&quot; /&gt;	
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
	Cyril Mottier is Mobile Software Engineer at Capitaine Train and Android Google Developer Expert. Passionate about technology and design, Cyril is an avid lover of Android and a multi-skilled engineer. He is actively involved in the Android community and shares his passion writing blog posts, creating open source librairies and giving talks. His motto: Do less, but do it insanely great.
	&lt;/p&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/prajyot-mainkar.jpg&quot; /&gt;	
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
    Mr. Prajyot Mainkar is the director at Androcid Media Pvt. Ltd, an app engineering firm based out of India. He is the manager of Google&#39;s Developer Group - GAUG ( Goa Android users Group) - one of the oldest android developer community in India. Being android developer himself, he has been active in the Android community and been assisting Android developers build new, compelling and well-received apps. He has spoken at several conferences including Droidcon India, GDG DevFest, Silicon India Mobile Conference and many more.
    &lt;/p&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/orhan-obut.jpg&quot; /&gt;	
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
    Orhan Obut is android developer at Rocket-Internet in Berlin. Since he is enthusiastic about android development and open-source, he is trying to learn as much as possible on these topics. He is also a big fan of open-source and constantly supports it. He has been worked on various projects from m-banking applications to m-commerce applications.  He always aims to use the software principles, the best practices and share the knowledge with the community.
    &lt;/p&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of &lt;a href=&quot;/github2015/sponsors&quot;&gt;sponsors&lt;/a&gt; support ADD has reached 28. Do not miss sponsorship opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/posts/support_en.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can support ADD by a blog post or any way you want. Just send us an email and we will put your logo among supporters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/posts/indirmobil_en.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.indir.com Mobile App Contest finalists will present their apps at Android Developer Days. Application to contest is still open and final date is 20 April. Winners will be announced in a Mobile Event organized by indir.com in Bahcesehir University on 23 May 2015. There are great prizes for the winners. For details click  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.indir.com/yarisma/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/posts/gdg_57.png&quot; /&gt;	
The number of GDGs as organizer has reached 57. The &lt;a href=&quot;/github2015/organizers&quot;&gt;organizers&lt;/a&gt; of ADD are from the cities of very different countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sponsors&quot;&gt;Sponsors&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please look at the &lt;a href=&quot;/github2015/sponsors&quot;&gt;Sponsors page&lt;/a&gt; to see the latest updates. All sponsors are listed here in e-mail version of this press bulletin.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 11:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.androiddeveloperdays.com/github2015/blog/march-newsletter</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.androiddeveloperdays.com/github2015/blog/march-newsletter</guid>
        
        
        <category>_i18n</category>
        
        <category>en</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>February Newsletter: Starting to announce Featured Speakers</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the February newsletter :) We will be sharing developments with you in this newsletter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/posts/02_statistics.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of people requesting participation to ADD has passed &lt;strong&gt;650&lt;/strong&gt;. Hurry up to participate and fill &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.eventbrite.com/e/android-developer-days-2015-registration-14846274607&quot;&gt;this form&lt;/a&gt;. Participation is still free :) Call For Papers is open now. You can submit a talk from &lt;a href=&quot;/github2015/blog/share-your-knowledge-and-experience-in-add/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/matt-sullivan.jpg&quot; /&gt;	
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
	Matt Sullivan is a developer advocate at Google where he helps people design and build cool health and fitness apps. He’s a big fan of conjuring up new ways to engage with users and motivate them to stay healthy using technologies like Google Fit, Android, Wear, Glass and many others to create novel fitness experiences. In previous lives he’s worked in varied fields such as cinema and theatrical software, bioinformatics and online collaboration tools.	
	&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/royi-benyossef.jpg&quot; /&gt;	
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
	Royi Benyossef has been an Android developer since before the first Android phone existed and proceeded to work on Android based tablets and TVs long before they were launched by Google so you might say i&#39;m an Android pioneer, as an avid Open source enthusiast i have been Organizing events as well as blogging and lecturing on Android related topics since 2008. Both of these facts have led to the fact that i am a Google developer expert since the program&#39;s inception which means that i&#39;m not a Google employee but Google believes that i know what i&#39;m talking about as well as how to say it.
	&lt;/p&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/muge-yilmaz.jpg&quot; /&gt;	
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
	As a Strategic Partner Manager at Google, Müge works with app developers who use In App Advertising as a channel for monetising their audience; either exclusively or complementary to in app purchase (IAP). She focuses on mApp ad monetization, App UX, Play Store optimization &amp;amp; customer retention and App Analytics. Prior her role in Google, she spent 4 years in IBM Turkey Software Group both in sales and sales advisory positions. Müge earned her master’s degree in Business Information Systems from Bogazici University. She currently lives in Dublin but travels her hometown, Istanbul frequently.
	&lt;/p&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/stephan-linzner.jpg&quot; /&gt;	
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
	Stephan Linzner is Senior Developer Platform Engineer Android at Google. He is an experienced Software Engineer, which has been working on the Android platform for more than 6 years. He is the creator of the Android Support Test library, contributor to Espresso. His mission is to help Android developers to build better quality apps by driven by tests.
	&lt;/p&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row speaker-row&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-3&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive img-circle&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/people/xavier-hallade.jpg&quot; /&gt;	
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;col-md-9&quot;&gt;
	Xavier Hallade is Developer Evangelist in Intel Software and Service Group in Paris, France.He is helping developers to improve their support for new hardware and technologies backed by Intel, with a focus on the Android NDK, Android TV and dual-displays.
	&lt;/p&gt;	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of &lt;a href=&quot;/github2015/sponsors&quot;&gt;sponsors&lt;/a&gt; support ADD has reached 21. Do not miss sponsorship opportunity.
&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/posts/gdg_57.png&quot; /&gt;	
The number of GDGs as organizer has reached 57. The &lt;a href=&quot;/github2015/organizers&quot;&gt;organizers&lt;/a&gt; of ADD are from the cities of very different countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sponsors&quot;&gt;Sponsors&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please look at the &lt;a href=&quot;/github2015/sponsors&quot;&gt;Sponsors page&lt;/a&gt; to see the latest updates. All sponsors are listed here in e-mail version of this press bulletin.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 11:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.androiddeveloperdays.com/github2015/blog/february-newsletter-starting-to-announce-featured-speakers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.androiddeveloperdays.com/github2015/blog/february-newsletter-starting-to-announce-featured-speakers</guid>
        
        
        <category>_i18n</category>
        
        <category>en</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Share Your Knowledge and Experience in ADD</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Developer events are great places for meeting other developers. You can learn many things from other developers. And also you can share your knowledge and experience with other developers. You can inspire many people with your talk. If you don’t want to miss this opportunity, you can apply and become a speaker at Android Developer Days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1YAAZMIJDBLwL55_Z0ZsHfgjkAJ47-FMSNzk8PL4ffB8/viewform?c=0&amp;amp;w=1&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary waves-effect waves-button waves-light waves-float horizontal-center&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Make Submission&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can submit any subject including the subjects below. Deadline for Call For Papers is &lt;strong&gt;1st April 2015&lt;/strong&gt;. Don’t be late, :) For attendees, register for free on:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.eventbrite.com/e/android-developer-days-2015-registration-14846274607&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary waves-effect waves-button waves-light waves-float horizontal-center&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Registration Web Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/posts/share-your-knowledge.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;subjects&quot;&gt;Subjects&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Future Technologies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile World
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Future of Mobile World&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;New Generation Mobile Devices (Wearable products, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Android OS
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Future Versions&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Android in Different Architectures&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Android in Different Areas(Industry, Defense, Home Electronics etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile Operating Systems(iOS, Tizen, Firefox OS, Windows Phone etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Android App Development
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;New Features and Capabilities&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;App Development Best Practises&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Android SDK Tools&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;UI(User Interface) / UX (User Experience) Design&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;App Monetization
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;App Marketing and Growth Hacking&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;In-app Billing&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;User Statistics&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;App Development in Mobile Operatins Systems(iOS, Tizen, Firefox OS, Windows Phone etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Android NDK&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cross Platform App Development Frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;HTML5&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Game Development&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Google TV&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Google Playstore&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Google Glass&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Communication Solutions (NFC, Bluetooth, Wi-fi)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3G, 4G Wide Band Communication&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cloud
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Google Cloud Messaging for Android&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Google App Engine&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Augmented Reality&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Social Media&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Location Based Services and Maps&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile Education&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile Payment&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Security&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Internet of Things&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Embedded Systems and Single Board Devices(Arduino, Raspberry PI, BeagleBoard, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Big Data Processing Optimizations in Mobile Devices&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Software Development Methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Success Stories&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Entrepreneurship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover we appreciate all different ideas and papers beyond subjects above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please let us know via &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:contact@androiddeveloperdays.com&quot;&gt;contact@androiddeveloperdays.com&lt;/a&gt;, if you have any question about call for papers, being attendee or sponsorship packages.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2015 11:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.androiddeveloperdays.com/github2015/blog/share-your-knowledge-and-experience-in-add</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.androiddeveloperdays.com/github2015/blog/share-your-knowledge-and-experience-in-add</guid>
        
        
        <category>_i18n</category>
        
        <category>en</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Android Developer Days 2015 Journey Has Started</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Challenge has started for Android Developer Days 2015 and lets be together in this journey.
Android Developer Days is going to take place in METU Cultural and Convention Center, Ankara, Turkey on May 11/12 2015. It is again free and open to everyone. GDGs (İstanbul, Eskişehir, Konya, Ankara, Düzce, Sivas and İzmir) in Turkey and METU IEEE takes part in organization committee of ADD. Moreover, we are again open to add new organizers to conference. Let’s be together and grow this community event together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.androiddeveloperdays.com/2014/&quot;&gt;How was ADD 2014?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;fb-root&quot; class=&quot;embed-responsive&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;(function(d, s, id) {  var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];  if (d.getElementById(id)) return;  js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id;  js.src = &quot;//connect.facebook.net/en_US/all.js#xfbml=1&quot;;  fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs);}(document, &#39;script&#39;, &#39;facebook-jssdk&#39;));&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fb-post&quot; data-href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.668204803216292.1073741830.595383730498400&amp;amp;type=1&quot; data-width=&quot;500&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fb-xfbml-parse-ignore&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.668204803216292.1073741830.595383730498400&amp;amp;type=1&quot;&gt;Post&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/androiddeveloperdays&quot;&gt;Android Developer Days&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;International (34) and local (25) speakers shared their knowledge and experiences about current and new mobile technologies. 29 GDGs from all around the world collaborated for this event to make it happen. The event was a blast with 2053+ attendees. Hackathon, sponsored by Turkcell,Nokia Developer and Alcatel One Touch, was organized as a subevent. In addition, hundreds of books, notebooks and bags were given away. 17 smartphones delivered to attendees. Shovel board game, Kinect Games, Virtual Reality Games and Mobile Games were played by attendees which makes the event more fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; src=&quot;/github2015/img/posts/add2014_infograph_en.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-time-for-add-2015&quot;&gt;The time for ADD 2015&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;support-community-to-be-together&quot;&gt;Support Community to Be Together&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ADD is an &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Open_conference&quot;&gt;Open Conference&lt;/a&gt;. Support the community and ADD to grow the community. Lets be together ! Bigger and richer ADD will be more beneficial to all of us. This conference is organized by volunteer people to improve the knowledge, experience and also expand the vision of attendees, so in order to make it more beneficial for community, you can support this conference. As a result if you want to be part of this organization and support it just keep in touch via &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:contact@androiddeveloperdays.com&quot;&gt;contact@androiddeveloperdays.com&lt;/a&gt;.
Lastly, here is the registration page of ADD 2015, you can register for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;//eventbrite.com/tickets-external?eid=14846274607&amp;amp;ref=etckt&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;260&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; marginwidth=&quot;5&quot; marginheight=&quot;5&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 11:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.androiddeveloperdays.com/github2015/blog/android-developers-days-2015-journey-has-started</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.androiddeveloperdays.com/github2015/blog/android-developers-days-2015-journey-has-started</guid>
        
        
        <category>_i18n</category>
        
        <category>en</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
